chazhound.com 2005-12-12

# Chazhound's Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement for Chazhound's Free Dog Page and  
The Chazhound Entertainment Network  

Chazhound has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate a firm commitment to privacy. Chazhound is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors and have been responsible website publishers since 1997.

**What information do we collect, and why?  
**
      
When you participate in our free information lists, or use our message forms, we may ask for your name, address, and other personal information. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.  
We monitor player traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and enhance the design of our web sites. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

**Chazound will not disclose your email address or any other personal information to other parties.  
**
      
Chazhound's advertisers and other partners do not receive any specific personal information. Chazhound only provides our advertisers and other partners with aggregate information or mass information used to show trends and patterns about the visitors using our site. Our advertisers are not ever provided with access to personal information which may identify you.  
As a member of one of our mailing lists, you will periodically receive e-mails featuring special offers and discounts managed through [PostMasterDirect.com](http://rentals.postmasterdirect.com/homepage/main?page=pledge.mhtml).  
If for any reason you would like to cancel a mailing list membership, you may do so at any time.  
The Dog-E-Zine is published monthly from FunnyPostcard.com.  

**Not accessible by visitors under 13 years old.**
    **  
** In compliance with [The Children's Online Protection Act](http://www.freereports.net/childrens_privacy_protection.html), this is a site which provides services to visitors over 13 years old. Anyone under the age 13 is not allowed to participate in any survey, free information lists, or any activity in which you have to enter any personal information. However, you may browse for fun.  

**Contact  
**
      
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:  

1\. Fax the following fax number:  
904-241-6741  
2\. Online at: [Chazhound Message Center](http://www.chazhound.com/mail.html)  

 **Conclusion**  

     Chazhound makes protecting your privacy a top priority. We want you to feel safe and in total control with your experiences with us. Our goal is to entertain and educate you on everyday life issues. Thank you for your continued support.  
Disclosures/Disclaimers   

Back

|   
---|---
